Rachel Florey - Bland

Leeds

07857328914

Rachel.florey89@icloud.com

I am a mature, capable individual who has currently 16 years of customer service experience, communicating effectively with colleagues and different levels of management including the general public from diverse backgrounds. This experience has allowed me to gain the necessary skill sets to progress throughout my customer service-based career. I continuously maintain a high level of customer service throughout any role, possessing the necessary enthusiasm, drive and motivation to achieve and succeed in each task I am instructed to or tasks where I have demonstrated my own initiative. I have a clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problem solving and a drive to see things through to completion. Willing to learn new skills and implement my existing skills to any role, creating a positive contribution to any employer.

Key Strengths

- Analytical thinking
- Ability to work in high-pressured environments
- Conflict resolution
- Planning
- Tenacity
- Team work

Employment History

Asda (Asda House) - Merchandising Helpdesk - April 2019 - Present day

- Providing assistance and support with merchandising queries direct from stores nationwide
- Asking detailed questions to determine nature of problem
- Walk stores through the internal online systems to allow them to be self sufficient
- First point of contact with difficult personal

NG Bailey - subcontractors for open reach Project management office (PMO) - June 2015 - Nov 2018

- Planning Fibre installations for 16 teams (nationwide) using in-house systems
- Working on Fibre projects such as (HSBC,NATWEST,SAINSBURYS/ARGOS concession
- Arranging Traffic management/Abseils (nationwide)
- Raising PO's for hire equipment
- Completing risk assessments and method statements (IOSH trained)
- Dealing direct with contract managers to secure contract (SIP)

Mitie - Customer Service (AB Inbev) - January 2015 - June 2015

- Allocating various different skilled engineers to resolve situations
- Multi skilled on all commissions around the business (banks, 02)
- Dealing with difficult customers on a daily basis (complaint lines)
- Provided advise to members of the public in business critical situations

Great Clothes - Store supervisor - June 2015 - Nov 2015

- Opened and closed the establishment on a daily basis
- Created a social media page (Facebook) to enhance footfall
- Money handling, cashing till, spot checks
- Developed a staff rota to create efficiency and to promote time keeping

Wage day advance - Customer Service Advisor - July 2014 - April 2015

Real time analyst - March 2015 - April

- Assisted customers process loans online, verbally and manually
- Allocated 30+ staff to inbound and outbound functions to create efficacy
- Arranged daily/weekly rotas for 30+ staff using data to maintain BAU.
- Adhered to FCA regulations (financial conduct Authority)
- Assisted with training new members of staff on the process and systems.
- Presented the SLA' targets, KPIs and presented to Office managers inc CEO

Sodexo Property Solutions - Technical services Scheduler - Nov 2013 - June 2014

<u>Sodexo Property Solutions</u> - Helpdesk operator - April 2013 - November 2013

- Managing inbound and outbound calls on a daily basis
- Ability to react to diverse situations such as Bank robberies
- Ensuring accuracy when inputting information/data into the house system

<u>UK Safety Management</u> Sales agent - July 2012 - November 2012

<u>Superdrug</u> - Sales Advisor - August 2006 - May 2012

Qualifications

- B-TEC Maths and English Level 2
- Customer service level 2
- IOSH trained
- 5 GCSE'S grade C-E

References available on request.